Guide to the Collection of pulp novels about bestiality, 1970-1979.
Collection of pulp novels about bestiality
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection of pulp novels about bestiality, 1970-1979.
7774
3 boxes (46 volumes), comprising .9 cubic foot.
books, printed material
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection of pulp novels about bestiality by various authors.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection of pulp novels about bestiality by various authors.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Bagley, H. L.; Bastion, Gary.; Benjamin, Jack.; Best, Harry.; Blustein, Arnold.; Canari, C.; Christy, Richard.; Christy, Richard.; Christy, Richard.; Como, Joseph.; Courtney, Dana.; Cummings, Felicia.; DeGranamour, A.; Duval, Nicole.; Elkhart, Arthur.; Everest, Jonathan.; Fox, Duncan.; Gable, Paul.; Gable, Paul.; Gallery, P. J.; Geis, Richard E.; Geis, Richard E.; Guntzinger, Otto.; Harris, Edwin.; Kroner, Emil.; L., Doris.; Lancing, Geoffrey.; Lee, Kelly.; Lee, Wysteria.; Lyons, May.; Martin, Rod.; Masters, Sylvia.; Mergen, Julius.; Miller, Alvin.; Pyne, Al.; R., Marilyn.; Rosenfeld, J. Rupert.; Roth, Damon.; Russell, Don.; Russell, Don.; Shepherd, W. R.; Stone, Jessica.; Weiss, Joe.
Subjects:
Bestiality; Sex; Erotic stories.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
NOTES
Collecting Program: Human Sexuality Collection.
Made-up set.
CONTAINER LIST
- Author last names A through D and anonymous (Box 1)
- Author last names E through L (Box 2)
- Author last names M through Z (Box 3)
- 3 Big Underground Classics in One Book- 7 In a Barn, On the Farm in Old Missouri, Another Night to Remember!!, 1971 (Box 1)
  Author: no author
- Female Domination of the Beasts- Volumes 1 and 2, 1971 (Box 1)
- The Beast Seekers, 1967 (Box 1)
  Author: H. L. Bagley
- Angel's Animal Nature, 1971 (Box 1)
  Author: Gary Bastion
- Coming With Her Collie, 1973 (Box 1)
  Author: Don Bellmore
- The Animal Lovers, no date (Box 1)
  Author: Jack Benjamin
- The Anatomy of a Neighbor, 1971 (Box 1)
  Author: Harry Best
- Beauties and Beasts, no date (Box 1)
  Author: Arnold Blustein
- Virgin's Bestial Lust, 1974 (Box 1)
  Author: C. Canari
- The Animal Lovers, 1967 (Box 1)
  Author: Richard Christy
- The Pony Lover, 1970 (Box 1)
- Bride of the Beasts, 1971 (Box 1)
- Man, Woman, and Beast, 1968 (Box 1)
  Author: Joseph Como
- Miss Blackwood's Strange Vacation, 1971 (Box 1)
  Author: Dana Courtney
- The Bestial Orgy, 1970 (Box 1)
  Author: Felilicia Cummings
- More of Mark of the Beast, 1972 (Box 1)
  Author: A. DeGranamour
- The Breeders, 1968 (Box 1)
  Author: Nicole Duval
- Animal Rapists, 1972 (Box 2)
  Author: Arthur Elkhart
- The Great Dane Scandal, 1970 (Box 2)
  Author: John Everest
- Bitch in Heat, 1973 (Box 2)
  Author: Duncan Fox
- Dog-Raped Coed, 1977 (Box 2)
  Author: Paul Gable
- Sister's Canine Habit, 1983 (Box 2)
- Bestial Blonde, 1971 (Box 2)
  Author: P. J. Gallery
- Women and Bestiality, 1971 (Box 2)
  Author: Richard E. Geis
- Women and Their Animal Lovers, 1976 (Box 2)
- The Animal Cult, 1968 (Box 2)
  Author: Otto Guntzinger
- Animals as Sex Partners, 1969 (Box 2)
  Author: Edwin Harris
- Passion for Animals, 1971 (Box 2)
  Author: Emil Kroner
- Modern Acts of Bestiality, 1969 (Box 2)
  Author: Doris L.
- After Daddy, Momma's Dog, 1976 (Box 2)
  Author: Geoffrey Lancina
- Boys, Girls, and Beasts, 1972 (Box 2)
  Author: Kelly Lee
- Dog Lover, 1971 (Box 2)
  Author: May Lyons
- Sex Acts Between Women and Animals, 1972 (Box 3)
  Author: Rob Martin
- Female Bestiality- 70, 1969 (Box 3)
  Author: Sylvia Masters
- Women Who Make Love to Their Animals, 1971 (Box 3)
  Author: Julius Mergen
- Two-Way Canine, 1981 (Box 3)
  Author: Alvin Miller
- Women and Their Dogs, 1972 (Box 3)
  Author: Al Pyne
- My Animal Harem, 1970 (Box 3)
  Author: Marilyn R.
- The Animal Lovers, 1967 (Box 3)
  Author: J. Rupert Rosenfeld
- Stag Starlet, 1971 (Box 3)
  Author: Damon Roth
- Wendy's Wolf, 1971 (Box 3)
  Author: Don Russel
- Molly's New Playmates, 1972 (Box 3)
- Dog Girl, 1973 (Box 3)
  Author: W. R. Shepherd
- Janet's Animal Affair, 1972 (Box 3)
  Author: Jessica Stone
- Strange Hang-Ups, 1970 (Box 3)
  Author: Joe Weiss